1 General Description 
	The SC92F8363B/8362B/8361B (hereinafter referred to as the SC92F836XB) is a kind of enhanced high-speed 1T 8051-based industrial Flash Microcontroller unit (MCU) with integrated TouchKey function, in which the instruction system is completely compatible with standard 8051 product series. 
	The SC92F836XB has a 23-channel dual-mode capacitor TouchKey circuit with low power consumption. The TouchKey circuit can be operated under STOP Mode.
	The SC92F836XB is integrated with 8K bytes Flash ROM, 1K bytes SRAM, 128 bytes EEPROM, up to 26 General-purpose I/Os (GPIO), 13 IO external interrupters, three 16-bit timers, 11-channel 12-bit high-precision ADC, 6-channel independent 10-bit PWM, internal ±1% high-precision 12/6/2MHz high-frequency  oscillator and 4% precision low-frequency 128K oscillator、 external crystal oscillator interface, one separate UART, one three-in-one serial communication interface which can be used as UART/SPI/TWI (SSI). To improve the reliability and simplify the circuit design, the SC92F836XB is also built in with 4-level optional LVR voltage, 2.4V ADC reference voltage and other high-reliability circuits. 
	The SC92F836XB features excellent anti-interference performance, which make it possible to be widely applied to industrial control system, such as intelligent home appliances, home automation, Internet of Things, wireless communication, gaming peripherals and consumer applications.

2 Features 
Operating Voltage: 
	2.4V ~ 5.5V
Operating Temperature: 
	-40 ~ 85℃
Package: 
	SC92F8363B (SOP28/TSSOP28)
	SC92F8362B (SOP20/TSSOP20)
	SC92F8361B (SOP16)
Core: 
	1T 8051
Flash ROM: 
	8K bytes Flash ROM (MOVC) prohibited addressing 0000H ~ 00FFH) can be rewritten for 10, 000 times
IAP: 
	Code option into 0K, 0.5K, 1K or 8K
EEPROM: 
	128 bytes EEPROM can be rewritten for 100, 000 times. The data written-in has more than 10-year preservation life.
SRAM: 
	Internal 256 bytes + external 768 bytes
System Clock (fSYS): 
	Built-in high-frequency 24MHz oscillator (fHRC): 
		As the system clock source, fSYS can be set to 12/6/2MHz by programmer selection. 
		Frequency Error: Suitable for 3.0V ~ 5.5V and -20 ~ 85℃ application environment, no more than ±1% of frequency error
	Built-in high-frequency Crystal Oscillator Circuit
		Available to externally connect 2-16 MHz Oscillator
		As the source of system clock, fSYS can be set to /2, /4 or /12 of the frequency of oscillator via code option.
	Operating voltage at different system frequency: 
		>12MHz @2.9 ~ 5.5V
		≤12MHz@2.4 ~ 5.5V
Built-in Low-Frequency 128kHz Oscillator (LRC): 
	Clock source of Base Timer (BTM), which can wake up the SC92F836XB from stop mode 
	Clock source of Watchdog (WDT)
	Frequency Error: 4.0V ~ 5.5V and -20 ~ 85℃ application environment, no more than ±4% of frequency error
Low-voltage Reset (LVR): 
	4-level LVR voltage options: 4.3V, 3.7V, 2.9V, 2.3V
	The default is the Code Option value selected by the user
Flash Programming and Emulation: 
	2-wire JTAG programming and emulation interface 
Interruption (INT): 
	12 interrupt sources: Timer0, Timer1, Timer2, INT0 ~ 2, ADC, PWM, UART, SSI, Base Timer and TK 
	3 external interrupt vectors shared by 13 interrupt ports, all of which can be defined in rising-edge, falling-edge or dual-edge trigger mode. 
	Two-level interrupt priority capability
Digital Peripheral: 
	Up to 26 bidirectional independently controllable I/O interfaces, able to configure pull-high resistor independently
	P0/P2 ports with 4-level drive capability 
	All I/Os equipped with sink current drive capability (70 mA)
	11-bit WDT with optional clock division ratio
	3 standard 80C51 Timer/Counters: Timer0, Timer1 and Timer2
	Timer2 can be set to capture mode
	Six 10-bit PWM output channels with variable period and individual duty cycle, which can simultaneously output three sets of complementary PWM waveforms with dead zone
	5 I/Os as output of the 1/2-bias LCD COM
	1 independent UART communication interface (Switchable I/O port)
	1 three-in-one serial communication interface (SSI) (Switchable I/O port) 
	16*16-bit hardware multiplier and divider unit (MDU)
Analog Peripheral: 
	The 23-channel dual-mode TouchKey (TK) circuit with low power consumption can be configured in high sensitivity mode or high reliability mode: 
		High-sensitivity mode applicable to TouchKey sensor, proximity induction and other TouchKey applications featuring high requirements on sensitivity 
		High reliability mode features very strong anti-interference which is able to pass 10V dynamic CS test 
		Implementing 23-channel high-sensitivity TouchKeys and derivative functions
		High-flexibility development with software library support to reduce development difficulty
		Supporting automatic debugging software and intelligent development 
		When scanning with a single TouchKey in stop mode, the overall power consumption of the chip can be as low as 11uA
	11-channel 12-bit ±2LSB ADC
		Built-in 2.4V reference voltage 
		2 options for ADC reference voltage: VDD and internal 2.4V
		Internal one-channel ADC, where VDD can be measured directly
		ADC conversion completion interrupt
Power Saving Mode: 
	IDLE Mode: can be woken up by any interrupt. 
STOP Mode: can be woken up by INT0 ~ 2、Base Timer and TK